rustylake.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy policy - RustyLake.com

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RustyLake.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.rustylake.com/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by RustyLake.com. We respect the privacy of our customers and the visitors of our website. 

Among other things, this means that we: clearly state the purposes for which we process personal data. We do this through our privacy policy. strive to limit our collection of personal data to only those personal data that are necessary for our purposes. ask for your explicit consent before processing your personal data when this is required. implement appropriate security measures to prevent loss and unauthorized access to your personal data. respect your right of inspection, correction and removal of your personal data, upon your request. 

**RustyLake.com may collect and use Users information for the following purposes:**

a. operate and improve offerings through the Site;  
b. help authenticate you when you are on the Site;  
c. remember your preferences and registration information, as the case may be;  
d. present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the Site offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications and;  
e. Advertisers on the Site might use information gathered by the use cookies and/or the web beacons for the purpose of online behavioral advertising and/or multisite advertising. Further information as regards the use of cookies and web beacons is set forth below. 

**Personal identification information**

In principle, a User can visit the Site without providing any personal data. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. When a User provides personal data on the part of the Site which consists, then he provides his consent to the Site to process these for the purposes mentioned Above. If these personal data concern another person than the User, then the User warrants that he is entitled to provide this consent on behalf of that other person. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns. 

**Cookies and web beacons**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer and is tied to information about the user. Whereas web beacons are mostly clear picture files which are used to keep track of a User’s navigation through a single website or a series of websites. 

Google Adsense ("Advertiser"), the Advertiser on the Site, might use "cookies" and/or "web beacons" for the purpose of online behavioral advertising and/or multisite advertising. The types of information that is gathered by the cookies and/or web beacons as well as the purpose(s) for which this information is used, are provided in the privacy policy of the Advertiser concerned. The User can consult the privacy policy of the Advertiser by clicking on the name of the Advertiser. 

\- Refuse cookies, web-beacons and online behavioral advertising 

To the extent that the User’s browser settings allow for the installation of cookies and web beacons on his computer, he consents with the installation of such cookies on his computer and he accepts that information relating to him may be used for behavioral advertising. The User of the Site has the right to object ("opt-out") against online behavioral advertising and the use of cookies or web beacons. Users can opt-out of cookies by visiting the Site of the Advertiser concerned or by visiting the website of the Network Advertisers Initiative at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

In addition, the User can refuse the installation of cookies and/or web beacons or delete them by adjusting the browser settings on his computer. If you need further explanation or details, please see AllAboutCookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. 

\- Liability for cookies and web beacons and third party websites 

The Site can not be held liable for the Advertisers’ cookies, web beacons or third party websites for whatever purposes pursued. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

**Security**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, Username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

**Your right of inspection, correction and removal**

You have the right to know, upon your request, which of your personal data is actually processed by us, if any. If any personal data we may have of you is incorrect, you may require us to correct it or remove it. If you do not want to receive any information from us about our services or products, please let us know. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Changes will be notified at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: info@2conceptnetwork.com 

This document was last updated on September 21, 2015
